Welcome to my YouTube channel Kushal
Sports World - Rahul Thakur. Today I have
brought a video in front of you which
can be very beneficial for you. Friends,
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance
Company has the requirement of Unit Manager,
Agency Manager, Branch Manager,
Activity Manager in HR Department, HR Manager in
Operations, IT etc.
All over India,
friends, this video is for your knowledge, so
please watch this video completely,
like and share this video and
subscribe to the channel so that
you can get information about the upcoming videos. Friends, it has happened
through this, as I told you, the
requirement of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance is all over India, there are different
profiles, friends, and let me talk about
it, if you are
starting your career, then this can be a good choice
for you. Similarly, the
Pressure Life Insurance which I have
chosen, friends, you know that its branch is
not all over India but all over the world,
friends, let's talk about its education, then the
number which should be there in it is
simple, your 1012, a little more and
graduation.  Friends, it is cool
because I would like to tell you that this
is a controlled job for them, friends, there is
no third party vendor in it, the
salary that comes from the data,
friends, let me talk about your such professional life
insurance, friends, I will talk about its
salary structure, if you have traction, then
you can earn from 18 to 20000 rupees a month,
friends, let me talk about if you have experience, if you have experience, then
it depends on your last salary
package, you gambled, how much was your salary package
and what you give to others, they
cheat at least from 15 percent to Kunar, whatever your last salary was,
friends, the word in it is
like I told you,
unit manager and in this, what is branch sales
manager in it, friends,
you will have to sell insurance, you will have to go into it, there is
total market place
work, friends, if you go to the
IT department, then your work should be
related to software and hardware, plus
if you go into operations, then you
should know customer handling and if friends, I
talk about this, your
Friends, you know that whatever
new damage occurs in facial skin and all its
documentation is
not done by HR, friends, so for better information,
friends, I will take you to my
laptop screen, here I will
tell you how you can apply for it
and how you
can apply for your job in it for different profiles,
friends, I want to tell you one thing in advance
that
you will not have to pay any charge for this job, this is a
private cost, so let me take
you to your mobile laptop screen, as
you can see, it has automatically
come on the laptop screen, friends,
here what you have to type is
ICICI, you have to
open the option, after opening it, friends, it will
come to you like this, then you will
click on this option,
after clicking, friends, it took some
time to open it, as you can see,
you write it, friends, see here it
comes Join Us and Employ Joint Adventure,
friends, if you
want to join by joining us,  Friends,
advisory means you have dreamt of
becoming an LIC advisor, friends, so you
can work with China on a full-time basis, friends, and if you want to become an employee, let me
tell you in the video, for an
employee,
it is written Z-10 Employee, so
when you click on it, friends,
after clicking,
an interface like this opens, in it you want to be a
part of a winning
team, okay, friends, so look in it,
it is written that genre role without that
support and how to succeed, which I am going to
tell you, friends,
subscribe daily, friends, as soon as you click,
you will have a complete
interface like this, friends, in this, let me
tell you that I have already told you to
subscribe and professional with a score of
not completed graduation and should have at
least residency and
subscribe for that,
experience in life insurance
industry is not required, so as
I told you that there are many
different types of jobs in it, like agency, agency  It
means that
you will have to route your team to your friends' fans,
after recruiting them you will
sell insurance to them. The second is bank
insurance. In this, friends, you will have to
sit in the bank and sell
insurance to all the customers who come here.
Direct marketing,
director marketing means that
friends, in this you will have to market wherever you go,
you will have to do daily
insurance and there is customer
service operation, you will have to sit in it. There are
no such things inside the office as I
told you friends and if I go to the bathroom
friends, see you are coming here every day,
like I would like to tell you that there is
a kind of writing clancy inside it,
after the policy, for
whatever alarms you want to do, a
whole team is formed for this, if you want to go
into human resources class, want to go
into IT, want to go into investment,
so friends, right now the Ricoh
is for all the professors in Britain all over India,
friends, as you can see,
now the disadvantaged friends is that you can apply for this app in
any field you want to go into,
friends, how will you have to apply for it,
but do the writing aside  To New
Heights you will click on this friends you
can click on it you will see
your photo will turn on in the snaps window friends
after coming on it it takes some time to open
after opening see friends something
like this interface will appear in front of you
see in this a lot of openings have come according to your
city in which you
live even after that if you
want to search friends then here this search
option is given plus location where you
want your experience if you
can click on search then I am Josh so
now you should write worry Meerut how many
job openings are there in Meerut right now SSC
is on Pocha Life Insurance
see this as I clicked on this
after this it came that relationship manager
is required in Meerut friends you should have 7 to 10 years
of experience there are five openings
on Meerut Road so on this friends it is not
necessary that you believe in this if this thing is being made
but if it is so then for pressure
friends you can apply in it to
apply friends there is equal
button given in it to apply when you click on that side
friends
After clicking on apply, some such
interface will come up in which they
ask for all the requirements from you, they do not ask for your wallet.
Friends, it is written first in this, what is the responsibility area of ​​Sara to apply for this job,
so please read it carefully, only
after reading it you will
apply for the job, friends. Now
I have applied, so
friends, what is being asked in this, it is not asking for my wallet, the
last one is asking for email
ID, my contact number and
date of birth and friends,
your resume should be on your screen in the browser,
here you will add the masala you have set,
after uploading, I have read, accept, comment,
conditions, job institute
conditions, after applying, you will
submit it, friends,
as I told you what is the criteria for a
job in ICICI Prudential Life Insurance
and how you
can search for yourself, how you can apply for the job,
I hope
friends, you liked the video  You must have liked it. If you liked it then please
like and share the video
and subscribe to the channel so that
you can get information about upcoming videos
[Music] The